AYETIGBO, DARE TOYIN (MPA)

9, SEUN ONI CLOSE, AROWOJOBA ESTATE, MARYLAND, LAGOS.

Tell: 07032177775, 07011216301.

Email: dareayetigbo2003@yahoo.com

With years of experience in diverse field of human endeavors, ranging from hospitality, Sales, administration, I possess excellent communication skills and I have the ability to relate with wide range of people. I enjoy learning new things and work under pressure.

AREA OF COMPETENCY

Administration | HR | SALES | PROSPECTING | NEGOTIATION | Area Sales | Outsourcing | Microsoft | Drawing marketing plan | Strong coordinating | Directing | Project management | SALES advisor | Data analyst | Inventory management | Humility | Kindness | Office management | Client management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FEDERICO MAHORA NIGERIA LIMITED

2016-Till date

Business development manager: Engaged in market research, product development, recruitment of sales agents, staffs and ad-hoc staffs, create market awareness through digital marketing, Street marketing, supervised and communicate with different departments, agents to foster sales goal attainment.

Client management and revenue generation: Trained customers service representatives on the effective use of the products and services and ways to communicate it to clients, resolving dispute among staffs, clients and management, increased the revenue base of the company by 10% quarterly. Help in expanding the company to different locations within the state.

SALES: Have so far achieved #40m in sales; make distribution of 1000 cartoons products daily to different locations.

JOHNSON ADEDOJA ADEWOPO FOUNDATION, Lagos

2015-2016

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT: Handle multifaceted clerical tasks (e.g. data entry, filling, records management and billing) as assistant to the director. Created PowerPoint presentations used for Executive meetings. Communicated to multiple departments to prepare for different charitable programs around Nigeria. Trusted to manage the office in the supervisor's absence, providing timely and effective information. Handle donations (in cash and in kind), help store them properly, and distributed to the appropriate department for discharging.

Coordination: made travel arrangements for Executives, Coordinated different meetings arrangements within and outside the state, prepare training documents for new volunteers.

2014-2015

OYO STATE MINISTRY OF HEALTH, IBADAN Administrative Assistant (NYSC):

Maintained accurate records of all the medical personnel in the state, assisted in project initiation, evaluation, implementation, monitoring and feedback, helped facilitate communication among different departments in the ministry, mobilized and allocate resources to different departments. In charge of procurements.

THE CRADLE HOSPITAL, LAGOS

2012

Medical Assistant Internship: Assessment of patients' vital signs (E.g. pulse, blood pressure and temperature) height and weight. Inventory procurement and control | maintained instruments and medical equipment | collected data on the previous health and surgical history from patients | collected specimens for lab tests | in charge of emails and calls.

NIYI FILM HOUSE, Ile Ife

2006-2008

Sales Representative: provide accurate information on production features, pricing and aftersales services | answer questions from clients on products and services | ensured racks are fully stocked | informed customers on the discounts and special offers | Provide feedback to both clients and managers.

TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

Advanced Excel | management | leadership | training | Mentorship | Humility | adaptability | writing skills | processing payments | Marketing

EDUCATION / TRAINING / CERTIFICATIONS

Master of Public Administration (MPA)| 2016 - 2018

Obafemi Awolowo University, Ile-Ife, Osun State **B.Tech. Anatomy | 2008 - 2014.**

Ladoke Akintola University of Technology, Ogbomosho, Oyo State

- ✓ Corporate Governance in Nigeria, Lagos 2017
- ✓ Health Safety & Environment Competence Development Course I& II 2013
- ✓ Student Christian Movement Biennial Conference 2012
- ✓ All Tertiary Institution Conference, Calabar 2012

REFERENCES

Available upon request